[
  {
    "question": "A의 발음은?",
    "correct": "에이"
  },
  {
    "question": "B의 발음은?",
    "correct": "비"
  },
  {
    "question": "C의 발음은?",
    "correct": "씨"
  },
  {
    "question": "D의 발음은?",
    "correct": "디"
  },
  {
    "question": "E의 발음은?",
    "correct": "이"
  },
  {
    "question": "F의 발음은?",
    "correct": "에프"
  },
  {
    "question": "G의 발음은?",
    "correct": "지(쥐)"
  },
  {
    "question": "H의 발음은?",
    "correct": "에이치"
  },
  {
    "question": "I의 발음은?",
    "correct": "아이"
  },
  {
    "question": "J의 발음은?",
    "correct": "제이"
  },
  {
    "question": "K의 발음은?",
    "correct": "케이"
  },
  {
    "question": "L의 발음은?",
    "correct": "엘"
  },
  {
    "question": "M의 발음은?",
    "correct": "엠"
  },
  {
    "question": "N의 발음은?",
    "correct": "엔"
  },
  {
    "question": "O의 발음은?",
    "correct": "오"
  },
  {
    "question": "P의 발음은?",
    "correct": "피"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q의 발음은?",
    "correct": "큐"
  },
  {
    "question": "R의 발음은?",
    "correct": "알"
  },
  {
    "question": "S의 발음은?",
    "correct": "에스"
  },
  {
    "question": "T의 발음은?",
    "correct": "티"
  },
  {
    "question": "U의 발음은?",
    "correct": "유"
  },
  {
    "question": "V의 발음은?",
    "correct": "브이"
  },
  {
    "question": "W의 발음은?",
    "correct": "더블유"
  },
  {
    "question": "X의 발음은?",
    "correct": "엑스"
  },
  {
    "question": "Y의 발음은?",
    "correct": "와이"
  },
  {
    "question": "Z의 발음은?",
    "correct": "지(제트)"
  }
]
